CESAR TOMATIS

Software Engineer



SUMMARY

I'm a proactive person, always looking for new challenges and eager to learn new technologies. I love teamwork.

I'm a software engineer with 5+ years of experience. Since the beginning of my professional career I've worked with mobile technologies such as Ionic and Xamarin and web technologies such as React and Angular. As time went by I started learning by my myself other technologies such as NodeJS with Express and MongoDB to be able to create complete applications by myself.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

P Barcelona, Spain

03/2020 - present

I'm currently developing my personal resume as a web application using **ReactJS** and **Hooks**.

MERN Stack Developer

P Barcelona, Spain

01/2020 - present

I'm currently developing a web app that allows users to create and share food recipes with other users. I'm using **ReactJS** with **Hooks** and **Redux** in the **front end** and **NodeJS** with **Express** and **MongoDB** in the **back end**.

Software Engineer

atSistemas - ♀ Barcelona, Spain

08/2019 - present

I'm currently working with **remote teams** distributed in Madrid and other cities from Spain.

Bank of Spain

3/2019 - present

I was involved in the last stages of the app development (using **lonic 4**). I was in charge of fixing the final bugs, developing the latest change requests and distributing the app using **Fabric.**

Ayanet Tic - Nutrinav App

01/2020 - 03/2020

I was involved in the last stages of the app development (using **lonic 4**). I was in charge of fixing the final bugs, developing the latest change requests and distributing the app using **Fabric.**

Vodafone

8 08/2019 - 01/2020

I was involved in the development of a mobile application built using **lonic 4**. I started this app from scratch, building the entire architecture. It was meant for internal use only, for sharing documents between users. These documents where stored using **blockchain** in the backend.

Front End Developer

Centrum - Rosario, Argentina

11/2018 - 03/2019

I developed a web application for a cosmetic clinic to manage appointments using **Angular 7**.

MEAN Stack Developer

UTN -

Rosario, Argentina

04/2018 - 04/2019

I developed a web booking management engine using **Angular 7** in the **front end** and **NodeJS** with **Express** and **MongoDB** in the **back end**.

EDUCATION

Systems Analyst

UTN - Facultad Regional Rosario
04/2019

First Certificate in English

University of Cambridge

LANGUAGES

Spanish Native ••••

English Proficient ••••

Italian Intermediate ••••

AWARDS

OZ Employee Recognition AwardCustomer Focus

FIND ME ONLINE

Personal Web cesartomatis.com

Control Linkedin Cesartomatis

GitHub cesartomatis

Stackoverflow /users/5175846/cesar-tomatis

Skype cesar.tomatis

TRAINING/COURSES

- React The complete guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux)
- Angular & NodeJS The MEAN Stack
 Guide
- Angular The complete guide
- The complete NodeJS developer course
- Create a CRUD application with Ionic
- Make Mobile VR Games in Unity with C#
- Game Physics Introducing
- Complete C# Unity Developer
- Design patterns in C# and .NET

Lead Mobile Developer

OZ - Rosario, Argentina

06/2015 - 05/2019

I've worked mainly with **mobile technologies** as a developer and ended up **leading** two different projects for the same client. In all the projects I worked with people that were at the same office than me and **remote teams** from the US.

Life's Abundance - Mobile App
 I was involved in the development of an application for managing vendors franchises using lonic and Angular. Is meant to be used on any device that runs iOS or Android.
 I was the TL of an Agile team (2 devs/ 1QA/ 1BA/ 1PM), following Scrum.

Client feedback:

https://followoz.com/resources/case-studies/wellness-company-fit-as-a-fiddle-after-software-systems-overhaul/#content

Life's Abundance - Warehouse App
 This app has been developed using Xamarin. Forms and is meant to be used only on iPad Mini 4. It's an app for internal usage to manage stock.

I was the **TL** of an **Agile** team (1 dev/ 1QA/ 1BA/ 1PM), following **Scrum**.

Client feedback:

https://followoz.com/resources/case-studies/wellness-company-fit-as-a-fiddle-after-software-systems-overhaul/#content

VR House Walkthrough
 I was part of the team (3 devs) involved in the development of an Oculus GearVR house walkthrough.

The application was made using **Unity Engine** and consisted in uploading the 3D models of a house and allow the user to walk through it and be able to see every detail of the house without the need of going to the physical place.

iPic Theaters - Mobile App
 This app has been developed using Ionic and Angular. Is meant to be used on any device that runs Android or iOS. It's a mobile booking solution for a premier luxury restaurant-and-movie theater.

Team of 4 devs, used **Agile** methodologies following **Scrum**.

I was part of a big **Agile** team (8 devs/ 2QA/ 1BA/ 1PO), following **Scrum**.

Android Developer

CeDITE - Rosario, Argentina

3 03/2015 - 12/2015

CeDITE stands for "Centro de Desarrollo e Investigación de Tecnologías Especiales" (Center for Development and Research of Special Technologies).

I worked developing **native Android** apps using **Java** and **Android Studio**. This apps helped people with Down Syndrome to improve their communication skills.

SKILLS

React	<u>Angular</u>	lonic
TypeScript	<u>JavaScript</u>	Redux
HMTL5	CSS3	SASS
Git	NodeJS	<u>MongoDB</u>
Express	Scrum	<u>Agile</u>
<u>Xamarin</u>	<u>C#</u>	<u>Heroku</u>
<u>Unity</u>	VR	SOL

REFERENCES

References upon request.